VIVEK KUMAR



PROFESSIONAL PROFILE

I'm Vivek and have 3 years of professional working experience in IT development. I love to code and I am very passionate about working with new technologies. I'm looking for an institution open to new ideas that will help me shape ideas into reality.

TECHNOLOGIES

- Flutter
- Python
- Django
- FastAPI
- HTML
- CSS
- Git
- Linux
- Android (Native)
- Docker
- CI/CD
- Node JS
- Server Deployment

CONTACT DETAILS:

Website: https://vivekkaushik.com

Email: me@vivekkaushik.com

Github: @iamvivekkaushik

LinkedIn: @iamvivekkaushik

WORK EXPERIENCE

EPIC Thoughtworks Pvt. Ltd.

May 2021 - Present

- Currently working here as a Senior Backend Developer.
- Working on a community management tool for admins and community managers, that integrates with Slack and provides a native experience.
- My responsibility includes the development of the backend for https://magik.so and creating deployment pipelines.
- Refrence: Mayank Nagpal (Founder) mayank@epyc.in

Civil Machines Technology

January 2019 - April 2021

- Worked here as an Android Developer and Tech Lead.
- Worked on multiple genres of products like E-Commerce,
 POS Systems, Backend Development, and Mobile Apps
- I was responsible for getting project requirements from the client and the development of it.
- Refrence: Himanshu Shankar (CEO) me@himanshus.com

EDUCATION

M.Sc. Computer Applications, Swami Vivekanand Subharti University

June 2019 - June 2021

PROJECTS

Date Picker Timeline

Flutter Open Source Package

- A flutter package that provides a date picker as a horizontal timeline.
- https://github.com/iamvivekkaushik/DatePickerTimelineFlutter

Awesome Card

A Flutter Open Source Package

- A flutter package to create a Credit Card widget in your application.
- Source Code is available at <u>https://github.com/iamvivekkaushik/AwesomeCard</u>

VIVEK KUMAR



PROJECTS

OTP Text Field

A Flutter Open Source Package

- A flutter package that provides OTP Field as a widget.
- https://github.com/iamvivekkaushik/OTPTextField

PROJECTS

Boitree

Django Backend

- A Link tree alternative where people can create a single link for their different profiles on the internet.
- We also added analytics for their page and all the links.
- https://biotree.now.sh